易考范文二十四
In the interesting drawing,
a beautifully-dressed woman is standing there,
a piece of red cloth covering her face.
However, when a man lifts the cloth, he is shocked to see an ugly face.
A word—advertisement—stands out on the cloth.
Obviously, the purpose of the drawing is to appeal to the public
for more concern about false advertising.
Now, we live in a world of advertisements,
which appear on mass media such as TV, radio, newspaper and magazine.
Usually, advertisers make a point of fine pictures, melodious music or charming stars,
which, in some cases, are merely a deceitful veil on fake merchandize.
Moreover, some advertisers boast about the effectiveness of the products,
but consumers sometimes are disappointed to find the products are not so good.
To solve the problem, my suggestions are as follows.
First, it is essential for consumers to use their reason to discern the authenticity of the ads.
In addition, advertisers should increase their awareness of public responsibility
to ensure the truthfulness of the ads they design.
At the same time, the media must ban ads as soon as they are found to be misleading and exaggerating.
Of course, we cannot solely rely on the morality of advertisers and the media,
because stronger supervision,
stricter laws and regulations play a more important role in eliminating deceptive advertisements.